impact on both net sales and co-operating income on our results and if mid-July rates
would prevail for the remainder of 2024, we would expect the full-year currency impact
to be negative 1 to 2 percentage points on net sales and negative 3 percentage points
on co-operating income.
And as a reminder, the estimated impact of exchange rates and our results are always
provided mid-month on our website.
I have two last.
Great.
Thank you, Harry.
So, before taking your questions, just to briefly summarize, continued momentum in quarter
two with sales up 11%, co-operating margin approaching 40%.
We see strong commercial execution, which I think demonstrates our ability to drive
our in-brand medicines, drive our growth brands, drive new launches, supports our bottom-line
guidance rates for full-year 2024.
Our pipeline continues to advance with the FDA submissions of Semblix in the first line
and AtraSense and IGAN are updated for setting Scali in early breast cancer.
And we're on track to achieve our mid-term guidance, 5% constant currency sales growth
through 2028, CAGR at 40% and a 40% co-operating margin by 2027.
So, we think a really great quarter for the company and we look forward to continuing
to drive strong performance through the remainder of this year.
So, with that, we can open the line for questions.
And as a summary, I would like to thank you all for joining us today.
Thank you.
As Sloane mentioned, please, one question per analyst, and then we'll come back through
the list again.
Thank you.
To ask a question, you will need to press star 1 and 1 on your telephone and wait for
your name to be announced.
To withdraw your question, please press star 1 and 1 again.
We will now take your first question.
And the question comes from the line of Emily Field from Barclays.
Please go ahead.
Hi.
Thank you so much for taking my question.
I just wanted to ask for a bit more context, just on the Natalie delay of the PDUFA in the
United States.
Can you confirm that this was very specific to the manufacturing issue and that the FDA
did not ask for any additional information with regards to any of the subgroups or any
additional information from the clinical trials?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thanks, Emily.
So, this was only related to the CMC issue where we've already initiated label discussions
with the FDA.
We submitted some additional documents.
I'm sorry.
We've already submitted some additional data to support the provision of the CMC package.
With that, we had the standard three-month extension because we had submitted that additional
data.
So, that extends the PDUFA out by three months.
We believe now we're well on track, having finalized the submission of that data for
an approval inside of Q3.
Next question, operator?
Thank you.
Your next question comes from the line of Florence Vespados from Barclays.
Your next question comes from the line of Florence Vespados from Bernstein.
Please go ahead.
Good afternoon.
Thank you very much for taking my question.
A quick question on cost antics and the new indication in HS.
Could you give us some color on how you see the HS opportunity going forward as it
seems that you are gaining new patients, you have a new treatment, more potent than the
existing one, but there will be also new entrants in the coming years.
So, some color on this HS market opportunity would be great.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thanks, Florent.
As you know, historically, only anti-TNFs, adalimumab was the only medicine available,
a biologic medicine available for these patients, and so I think the market had not grown
to its full potential.
I mean, HS is a relatively prevalent dermatological disease, I think the second most prevalent
after psoriasis, so something that, or a second or third most prevalent after psoriasis.